// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What does fitness mean?",
    answer: "None of the above",
    options: [
      "The ability to run 20 kilometers without fatigue",
      "To be able to lift 100 kilos maximum bench press",
      "To meet the demands of your environment",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The ability to change direction quickly and precisely and yet retain balance is the definition of which component of fitness",
    answer: "Agility",
    options: [
      "Agility",
      "Balance",
      "Coordination",
      "FLexibility"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Working for 20 minutes or more without stopping and heart rate of 75% of maximum ",
    answer: "Is continuous training",
    options: [
      "Is continuous training",
      "Is fartlek training",
      "Is interval training",
      "Is repetition training"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Overload is:",
    answer: "when you work harder than normal to increase the stress on the body systems",
    options: [
      "when you work too hard in training and have to stop",
      "when you work too hard over a period of training sessions and get injured",
      "when you work harder than normal to increase the stress on the body systems",
      "trying to lift too heavier a weight in a resistance training session"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "According to WHO recommendations, how much time daily do we need to engage in physical activity for our wellbeing?",
    answer: "30 minutes",
    options: [
      "10 minutes",
      "1 hour",
      "30 minutes",
      "SUbjective"
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "Keeping accountable to one another's phsycial health is going to contribute to the spread of the virus",
      answer: "False",
      options: [
        "True",
        "False",
      ]
 },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "Which statement below is correct?",
      answer: "SARS-CoV-2 causes COVID-19",
      options: [
        "COVID-19 causes SARS-CoV-2",
        "SARS-CoV-2 causes COVID-19",
        "Omo, Covid is fake",
        "No Idea"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "The South African mutation of the virus is:",
      answer: "more contagious",
      options: [
        "COVID-20",
        "more deadly",
        "more contagious",
        "more deadly and more contagious"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "Physical Exercise can help you grow new brain cells",
      answer: "True",
      options: [
        "Lie",
        "True",
        "False",
        "Maybe"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "For optimum performance, scientist recommend:",
      answer: "6-8 hours of sleep",
      options: [
        "6-8 hours of sleep",
        "9 hours or more of sleep",
        "7 hours of sleep",
        "Depends on you"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "Warning: Don't Try this at Home!!! What is the longest time experimentally proven, man has gone without sleep? ",
      answer: "11 days",
      options: [
        "11 days",
        "1 week",
        "5 days",
        "3 days"
      ]
    },


